Report!
General, the Empress Dowager is missing.
What?
The camp is crude.
I cannot bear to see the Empress Dowager suffer.
So I took her to stay with the Helian clan for a few days.
When the Great General returns,
she will be sent back immediately.
Helian Jie has abducted the Empress Dowager.
Men, assemble the troops and head to the Helian clan immediately.
Wait.
Young General, what do you mean?
You guard this place.
Leave this matter to me.
Thank you, Young General.
General,
are we just going to let this go?
It doesn't matter.
The gold vein is the most important thing.
There can be no mistakes.
Otherwise, if the Great General blames us,
I won't be able to bear it.
Besides,
we met the Empress Dowager by accident,
and now she's been taken away by Helian Jie.
Even if trouble arises in the future,
it has nothing to do with me.
Understood.
Let's go.
Young Master.
Where is Her Ladyship?
Where is she now?
Aren't you quite good at predicting things?
Do you still need me to tell you?
Return to Wuse City.
Why are you suddenly in a rush to return to Wuse City?
A'man secretly kidnapped Ji Mingyue.
The Helian Clan has long been oppressed by the imperial court.
Every year on the Empress Dowager's birthday,
the court would take the opportunity to demand an additional 50,000 taels of gold as tribute.
The entire Helian Clan has hated her to the bone for a long time.
If she is brought to the Helian Clan now,
not only will she be in danger,
but the Helian Clan will also be pushed to the forefront of the storm.
A'man's action
undoubtedly adds fuel to the fire.
A'man
is too willful.
Are you going to find her?
Of course.
Greetings, young master.
Empress Dowager.
Don't look at me like that.
I just used a little trick
so you can't use your magic.
Without your magic
and the unique acupoint sealing technique
of our Helian clan,
you
can't undo it.
Young Master, they are...
The Demon Empress, Ji Mingyue.
What?
Take them inside.
Yes, sir.
Move!
Hurry up!
Young Master.
The letter you told me to send to General Shen in the capital
has been delivered.
Good.
Shen Lian is coming too.
Then Wuse City
will have its liveliest day in history.
Shen Lian is coming.
Does the High Priest know?
My father is in seclusion.
He doesn't need to know.
That bitch used my father for years.
It's time for her to pay.
Shen Lian.
The Emperor has his eyes on her.
I'm afraid she won't be able to leave the city.
You underestimate her.
She is formidable.
She values wealth and power above all.
Tell me,
if she hears Baili Jinghong was secretly assassinated by my brother,
that several gold veins are now ownerless,
and that she is desperately needed
to take charge,
could she resist coming?
Give me back my son!
Demon Empress!
Demon Empress,
you ruined our country!
Give me back my son!
Demon Empress,
go to hell!
Go to hell!
Demon Empress,
you ruined our country!
It's all your fault!
Demon Empress!
How dare you harm us!
Why don't you just die?
Demon Empress,
beat her to death!
The corruption of a dynasty
always uses women as scapegoats.
A hundred years from now,
will history books also claim
that I am the demon empress who ruined the Dayin court?
It's ridiculous. Why?
Why does history only blame women for ruining the country,
but never records their merits and achievements?
Why are women merely tools to bear shame
and infamous reputations?
It is only because, since ancient times,
no woman has ever sat on the supreme throne.
Therefore, the snobbish masses
never speak up for them.
How do you have the nerve to live?
Demon Empress!
You monster!
Die!
How do you still have the nerve to live?
Just die, Demon Empress!
The eldest young master has returned to the city!
The eldest young master is back!
Eldest young master!
Go, bathe Her Grace and change her clothes.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Please don't blame me for sealing your acupoints again.
Your methods are too formidable.
I was forced to do this.
I have no choice but to wrong you.
Your Highness, are you satisfied with this one?
Change the pearl hairpin.
This one is too tacky.
Brother won't like it.
Yes.
Then how about this one?
Dressed up like this,
Your Highness is truly stunning.
Don't worry. I have no interest in you.
Aman is of great importance.
Where exactly is the Empress Dowager?
Don't rush, brother.
Get some rest.
You will see her soon.
There have been many coincidences on this journey.
What is going on?
Mother, why are you here?
If I hadn't come,
how would I know you've completely lost your mind?
Ji Mingyue is just a stepping stone in our plan.
Instead of figuring out how to take over
all of Baili Jinghong's gold veins,
you actually fell for her at a time like this.
If Helian Jie hadn't told me,
I wouldn't have believed it.
You've only seen her a few times,
and you already like her?
When I was young,
my father doted on me.
He sent the best guards to protect me
and the best painters to make me happy.
But I just couldn't be happy no matter what.
Mother, do you know why?
Because everyone had a mother,
except me.
After Aman was born,
he was sickly.
Father cared for him so much
that he liked me less.
I became even more unhappy.
Countless times, I fantasized
and wondered:
Did my mother
not love me?
Otherwise,
why didn't she come to see me?
Jin.
Later, I found out
that a child took my place
and became Mother's child.
So I sent painters and guards
to secretly record their lives
for me to imagine.
Mother treated her so well.
In summer, you would push her on the swing
and teach her archery yourself.
You would even personally
make her tremella and lotus seed soup.
To this day,
I haven't even tasted
the lotus seed soup you made.
I was really jealous of her then.
My jealousy turned into hatred.
I couldn't accept it.
Why could she take my place
and get your love?
But later she entered the palace,
eliminated enemies for you,
and was labeled a disaster to the country.
She was insulted
and became a demon queen everyone wanted to kill.
Then I started to feel guilty and blamed myself.
Was it
because of me
that a girl had to bear
the responsibilities I should have borne?
Why are you comparing yourself to her?
She's just from the General's manor,
a piece of trash born to a lowly servant.
It was I who taught her consistently for ten years,
so she could have her current skills.
But you're different.
You are extraordinarily gifted.
She can't compare to you at all.
You're wrong, Mother.
She is not trash.
She is the light in my heart.
You are right.
I really haven't seen her many times.
But it feels like
I have loved her for a very long time.
Just like
from the day I started expecting you to love me,
that long.
What is it?
To answer the First Young Master,
I wanted to see if the Empress Dowager
needed any water.
What did you say?
Empress Dowager?
Yes.
You may leave first.
Mingyue,
I...
Is this the truth?
So I'm not your child.
I'm just a pawn you raised from childhood.
A piece of trash born to a lowly maid of the General's Manor.
A stepping stone.
Your child
is him.
Young General Jiuying of the Northern Frontier.
Helian Jin of the Helian Clan.
Very well.
Deceiving me over and over again.
You truly are mother and son.
Cut the crap.
Give me the ledger.
Even now,
you're still thinking about the ledger.
Give me the ledger.
Hurry up.
Mother, we can talk about the ledger later.
Let's first...